迈克 · 诺斯: 在这种情况下,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: In this situation,
我们只是用另一种方式提供了初始化器。
w're just providing an initializer
by kind of another means.
我们可以像属性初始值设定项一样轻松地移动它。
We could just as easily moved this
up as a property initializer.
但我要指出的是，我们可以在任何地方做到这一点。
But I'm pointing out that
we can do in either place.
另外，如果我的打字稿设置正确的话。
Additionally, if my TypeScript settings
are correct here and they are.
你会注意到我们在这里被大喊大叫，忽略这第一条信息。
You'll note that we're getting yelled
at here, ignore this first message.
我们只是看到很多，因为我们有很多的课程和从来没有读过的东西,
We just see that a lot, cuz we have a lot
of classes and things that are never read,
因为这只是一页例子。
cuz it's just a page of examples.
这个错误消息很有趣，密码没有初始值设定项，并且
This error message is interesting,
password has no initializer and
构造函数中没有明确指定。
it's not definitely assigned
in the constructor.
我们现在看到的是，我们已经说明了 password 是一个字符串。
So what we're seeing here is we've
stated that password is a string.
对于任何下游代码,
And for any downstream code,
任何方法，他们都有可能进入私人领域。
any methods, they might be
able to access private field.
如果他们尝试访问密码，他们希望得到一个字符串返回，并且
If they try to access password they
expect to get a string back, and
目前这是不可能的。
currently that's not going to happen.
即使我们在这里有一个条件，如果我们说如果(电话0)。
Even if we had a condition here where
if we said like if (phone &gt; 0).
初始化这个，我们仍然会得到一个错误，因为分析
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Initialize this,
we'll still get an error because analyzing
不同的路径，我们可以通过我们的承包商。
the various paths,
we can take though our contractor.
一个或多个已被确定在哪里
One or more have been identified where
我们不会最终设置密码的值。
we would not end up setting
passwords up with the value.
我们有几种方法可以解决这个问题。
There are couple ways we can handle this.
一种方法是确定这就是问题所在,
One way would be to decide
that this is the problem,
我们应该始终初始化密码。
we just should always
initiatialize password.
另一种方法是增加这种可能性，即这种可能性是未定义的。
The other way would be to add
the possibility that this is undefined.
现在，任何人试图访问密码，他们会得到字符串或未定义。
And now anyone who attempts to access
password, they'll get string or undefined.
他们必须使用我们之前展示过的那些警卫中的一个。
They'll have to use one of those guards
that we showed an example of before.
如果(this.password) ，那么在该块密码中将是一个字符串。
If (this.password), and then within
that block password will be a string.
所以这是我们可以做的一件事。
So that's one thing we could do.
还有一件事我们可以做。
Here's another thing we could do.
我们可以使用一个新的操作员，这是一个我们想使用的
We could use a new operator here and
this is one we'd wanna use
如果我们真的知道那个电话号码，就像它肯定大于零一样。
if we really know that phone number like
it's guaranteed to be greater than zero.
基本上你知道
Basically you know for
事实上，你总是会走下去，一切都会好起来的。
a fact that you're always gonna go down
this branch and it's gonna be okay.
或者每次你实例化这个类,
Or maybe every time you
instantiate this class,
你在它上面调用一个方法来进行异步设置，对吗？
you call a method on it to do
some asynchronous setup, right?
比如我们这么做。
Like if we did this.
一个异步 init 函数,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: An asynchronous
init function,
没有办法让构造函数异步。
there's no way to make
a constructor asynchronous.
对不起，我一直保存在自动格式的东西。
Sorry, I keep saving
in things auto-format.
没有办法制造异步的东西，但也许我们就是知道
There's no way to make something
asynchronous, but perhaps we just know
无论我们在哪里使用它，在我们构建它之后，我们称之为 init
that wherever we use this, right after
we construct it we call init and
那么下游的所有东西都应该依赖于密码。
then everything downstream should be
able to depend on password being there.
在这种情况下，我们将使用所谓的定义赋值操作符
In this case, we would use something
called the definite assignment operator
这是一个叹号。
and it is an exclamation mark.
这就是说相信我打字稿,
What this is saying is
trust me TypeScript,
我负责确保这个字段被正确地初始化。
I'm taking responsibility for making sure
that this field gets initialized properly.
所以我希望你们能让我来处理这个问题
So this is an area where I want
you to let me handle this and
不要在代码的这一点上造成错误。
don't cause an error at
this point in the code.
那么，我的另一个有用的地方在哪里呢？
So, where my another useful place for
this kind of thing be?
如果你使用过棱角，反应，灰烬，聚合物，或 Vue，请举手？
Raise your hand if you've used Angular,
React, Ember, Polymer, or Vue?
太棒了，那么，您是否发现您最终直接实例化了组件？
Awesome, so, do you find that you end
up directly instantiating components?
您有一个组件类，您是否发现您曾经调用过新组件，以及
You have a component class, do you find
you are ever calling new component, and
然后渲染它并将该元素放入 DOM 中，或者
then rendering it and
putting that element in the DOM, or
这个框架能帮你解决吗？
is the framework handling it for you?
框架为您处理它。
Framework handles it for you.
所以通常有生命周期挂钩，你可能在那里设置东西,
So there are often life cycle hooks
where you might be setting things up,
建立属性。
setting up properties.
在早期的生命周期钩子中，您可能需要设置密码。
And in an early life cycle hook, you might
take care of putting password in place.
你们应该知道这是第一个叫法,
And you just know that this is the first
thing that is gonna be called,
构造函数的框架。
the frameworks doing
the constructor stuff.
我会负起责任的我知道有一个小小的差距,
I'll take responsibility,
I know there's this little gap,
在生命周期的早期，密码不在那里，但实际上,
very early in the life cycle, where
password's not there, but realistically,
我不会用那些代码做任何事情。
I'm not doing anything with that code.
这就简化了下游的东西,
And that simplifies downstream stuff,
你只需要输入密码，相信密码就在那里。
where you can just access password,
and trust that it will be there.
这里还有一个相关的提示。
Here's another related tip.
现实地说，我们不知道密码是否一定是
Let's say that realistically we don't know
if passwords are gonna necessarily be
在那里，也许在它生命周期的中期。
there, maybe in the middle
of its life cycle.
你的零件可能会有用，对吧？
Your component might get something, right?
你还是想把事情简化一点。
And you still wanna simplify things a bit.
我会做这样的事。
I would do something like this.
迈克 · 诺斯: 我会有一个潜在的价值
&gt;&gt; Mike North: I would have a value
that has the potential to be
迈克 · 诺斯: 还有
undefined,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: And
我可以做私人获取密码。
I could do private get password.
这只是一个 ecmascript5获得者，ES5获得者，它已经工作了很长时间。
This is just a ECMAScript 5 getter,
ES5 getter, it's worked for a long time.
它在 IE11和 ie10中工作。
It works natively in IE11 and 10.
如果密码值不存在，我们将懒惰地创建它,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: If the password value
doesn't exist, we'll create it lazily,
迈克 · 诺斯: 然后还回去。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: And then return it.
迈克 · 诺斯: 我们可以说这绝对是一根绳子。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: And
we can say this is definitely a string.
最终的结果是，在这里，我们有一个属性，它是一个字符串和
The end result is, here,
we have a property that's a string and
我们可以访问密码，无论我们需要它，它是懒惰创建。
we can access password wherever
we need it, it's lazily created.
我们第一次请求它，然后它缓存在实例上。
The first time we ask for it and
then it's cached on the instance.
所以我们可以不断地要求,
And so we could repeatedly go ahead and
keep asking for it,
我们还是实例化过一次。
we still instantiate it once.
但这是另一个技巧，对于那些开始时可能没有定义的东西
But this is another trick for
things that may start out as undefined and
你可以像这样创建一个懒惰的实例化值。
you can kind of create a lazily
instantiated value like this.
迈克 · 诺斯: 有问题吗？
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Questions?
酷，这应该是大部分常规的 JavaScript 的东西，尤其是。
Cool, this should be mostly regular
JavaScript stuff, especially that.
这是一种未充分利用，但吸气剂已经存在了一段时间。
It's kind of underutilized but
getters have been around for a while.